[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sprite was originally made in Germany.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Depression can cause brain damage.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following famous people is NOT a Marylander?", "correct_answer": "Valerie Bertinelli", "incorrect_answers": ["John Wilkes Booth", "Frederick Douglass", "Tom Clancy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were born in 1981, 1993 or 2005, what would your lunar sign be?", "correct_answer": "rooster", "incorrect_answers": ["rabbit", "monkey", "dragon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names refers to or is a synonym for red blood cells?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Haematids", "RBCs", "Erythrocytes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What condition is characterized by fear of hurricanes?", "correct_answer": "Lilapsophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Chirophobia", "Pagophobia", "Stenophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what continent is the watermelon plant believed to have originated?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "Asia", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie, directed by Bo Welch, won the 2003 Raspberry award in the category, Worst Excuse for an Actual Movie.", "correct_answer": "Cat in the Hat", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlies Angels:Full Throttle", "Gigli", "From Justin to Kelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the diet of the Sumatran rhinoceros?", "correct_answer": "It feeds mainly in the morning and before dusk.", "incorrect_answers": ["It consumes about 220 lb (100 kg) of food daily.", "All of these", "Its diet is rich in protein and poor in fiber."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Buzz Aldrin made a guest star appearance in an episode of The Simpsons. What was his comment when Homer Simpson showed no recognition of him being the second man to walk on the Moon?", "correct_answer": "Second comes right after first!", "incorrect_answers": ["Hey, I was just a second late!", "Im famous, the rest is history.", "How many times have you been on the Moon?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what holiday is the Spanish dessert called turron traditionally eaten?", "correct_answer": "Christmas", "incorrect_answers": ["Easter", "All of these", "New Years Eve"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The carnation is the national flower of this European country.", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Scotland", "Germany"]}]